subsidesports.com 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Subside Sports takes the subject of protecting your personal information very seriously.

Consent

The use of the Subside Sports websites implies that you agree to the terms of the Subside Sports Ltd online Privacy Policy. Should you not wish to agree to these terms then please do not use our websites.

Personal Information

When visiting the Subside Sports website then you may be asked to submit personal details in order complete your order. Submitting these details is optional, but necessary if you wish to order with our company.

Submitting these details implies that you understand and agree that Subside Sports and its subsidiaries and affiliates may transfer, store and process your personal information.

Subside Sports retains this information to support the transaction and any other activity you have elected to participate in. This includes newsletters, competitions and other marketing activity. If you wish to be removed from this list at any time then we will honor your request.

Your information is stored on 128-bit secure servers and is password protected. We recommend that you do not share this information with anyone.

Customer Registration

When placing an order you may be asked to create a customer account. This is purely to allow you to enter your data once and then access via a username and password.

To comply with Data Protection laws we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology for data transfer. SSL is an industry standard for managing the security of message transmission on the Internet through public-and-private key encryption and a digital certificate that secures our server compliance when doing Internet business or other on-line transactions. Subside Sports certificate is issued by Geocerts. When you are asked to enter any personal details or credit card information the web site will be secure. This is indicated with an icon at the bottom of your browser window resembling an unbroken key or a closed lock icon. SSL ensures that the information being sent is secure. Customer card details are then encrypted and a unique transaction reference number used in future data transfer.

Data Protection

Subside Sports Ltd is registered in accordance with United Kingdom Data Protection Legislation and will hold and use your personal data strictly in accordance with UK Data Protection Legislation.
